Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Asta and Yuno have arrived at the royal capital of the Clover Kingdom.
The magic knights are revered throughout the land.
The exam to determine who is worthy enough to join their ranks is about to begin.
Talmud
You're lying to me type of doubt
I know I know I know
Will out 15 years here
I remember moving all my dreams
夢はすら全て越えて あの日描いた僕が僕であるために いつの日だページの続けが今日 君と言う希望と
まるでいつかのワンページのような 君と僕ら出会えた これを奇跡って呼ぼうか
You
So cool
Whoa
Amazing nice and fresh won't be long now. Just a minute and you can get it while it's hot. Oh, that looks so good
Wow awesome check out all these swords and stuff
This place is a far cry from the village, huh?
Hey, is that where the wizard King lives
Probably the country's came to
Pretty nice, especially since it's gonna be my castle someday
My castle you mean
Nah, I might let you live there though
If you're lucky, I'll let you live there
Hush, you're all right, sweetie. Don't cry. Come on. We need to hurry back and get the shop ready
Reminds me of everyone back at the church
I feel sorry for them. It's gotta be really lonely without me there
Yeah
Hey, wait up
You know
Ah, peace and quiet at last. Things sure are nice around here with Ostagon
You don't mean that Nash
What? Of course I do
They'll be arriving at the Royal Capital about now
I feel so nervous for them
I hope the exam goes well
Yeah, me too
Huh?
I didn't say anything
Asta
You know
Good luck boys
Ah
Yeah
So, where's this exam happening anyway?
Over there, I think
What is that?
Grilled violet steak on a stick
It was super cheap
Come and get your grilled violet steak fresh off the fire
Raised humanely and sourced responsibly
You wanna bite?
I'll pass
Chock full of nutrients that'll keep you going
Yeah, sure
Come on
It's this way
Good luck on the exam
The Clover Kingdom's rising stars
The future of the kingdom is round value
You can do it
I won't let you down, don't worry
I don't know him, I don't know him
There we go, you're number 163
Well, next
Name's Yuno, from Haj
Yuno from Haj, alright
And your grimoire?
Four leaf clover?
You've heard the rumors, right?
Hey look, it's that grimoire
No way, a four leaf clover?
Oh wow
Right, you're number 164
Next
I came here from Haj too, I'm Asta
And here's my grimoire
Ah, not really in great shape, is it?
Are you sure that's a grimoire?
What? Of course I'm sure, come on, take a good look
There, see? See?
Alright, back off please
You're number 165
Yes!
Woohoo!
Coming all this way from some no-name village
Quite motivated, aren't they?
Ugh, starting to get nervous now
Hey, what's up with these crazy birds?
Anti-birds, mainstays of the exam hall
What, these things?
Everybody knows the lower your magic power, the more birds you attract
Yeah, whatever
Hey, look, see that guy?
There are no birds anywhere near him
Yeah, it's that guy from before
Which one?
He's from this podunk village called Haj or something
I don't know how he got a four leaf clover, grimoire
What? No way, you're kidding
Ha ha ha!
One of us is gonna be the wizard kid!
This is where our legend begins
Right, you know?
He's not really serious, is he?
I've been training for this the last six months
Wait till you see what I can do
Why are they trying to kill me?
Ha ha ha, what the hell?
Poor schmuck
Not the nicest welcome to the big city
Get the hell away from me!
Ha ha ha!
Phew, guess they finally had enough
Hey there, sorry about that
You got a death wish, boy
Death wish, boy
Who is this guy?
He's got the eyes of a killer
That neck!
Mages don't have necks that thick!
And the way he carries himself
How can we be the same age?
Wait, hold on
No judging a book by its cover
Just be nice and friendly to him
Wow, you look really old for your age
Must have had a rough life, huh?
Ha ha!
Looks like I was right about that death wish
This book's got the right cover!
Finally, there you are
What are you doing out here anyway?
Right now, getting ready to wring this kid's neck
Ha ha ha ha!
Hey, is that who I think it is?
Yeah, it's him!
Unreal ruler case!
Wielder of the rare spatial magic!
And who is this lovely lady?
The womanizer who spends more time flirting than doing his job
And that's...
Gordon Agrippa!
He's a hex magic expert!
Word is that he's got some issues with communicating
Plus he's scary
Hey now, stop!
That won't do it all!
A squad captain can't kill an examinee
Why'd you even come down here in the first place?
Went to take a dump and got lost
Wait, he said squad captain!
Which means that guy must be...
Ten
Yami Sukihiro God of Destruction
What are you counting down to?
The end of your little life
Yami? The captain of the black bulls?
As in the squad of scoundrels who do more harm than good?
Those black bulls?
There's not a single person on that squad who doesn't have a screw loose
One's a shameless flirt, one's mute
What are the rest of them like?
Man, I hope I don't end up on that squad
Why did I pick the wrong guy to run into?
My head's gonna explode!
result
THREE, TWO, ONE
Well now, look at that
The exam is about to begin
T zo'n
That was a close one, boy
You got a second chance at life
Better do something with it or I'll come back and kill you
See you later.
I wish the captain would just kill me instead.
That was a whole lot of not fun.
Is your head feeling all right?
Uh, yeah.
Confronting Captain Yami of the Black Bulls without warning like that?
I can't say I envy you.
Oh, I'm Seke, by the way. Seke Bronzatsa. It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, same to you. I'm Asta.
That's Nozel Silva, the captain of the Silver Eagles.
One of them.
A real Magic Knight squad, Captain. Interesting hairstyle.
How does he see with that thing in his face?
Fuegolion Vermillion. Captain of the Crimson Lions.
As his name suggests, he's a Flame Creation Magic user.
Wow.
Jack the Ripper. Captain of the Green Praying Mantises.
Wait, what's a praying mantis?
That long, thin, green bug.
Captain Jack can rend the very earth in two with his severing magic.
Whoa, that's awesome!
Praying mantises, though? Seriously? Who wants to be named for a bug?
Next, we have Miss Charlotte Roselay. Captain of the Blue Rose Knights. Just look. She's so beautiful.
Eh, she's got nothing on Sister Lily.
Go there, Poizot. Captain of the Purple Orcas.
That's all you got?
The shabbier ones don't interest me.
Dorothy Unsworth. Captain of the Coral Peacocks.
Is she sleepwalking?
She doesn't do anything but sleep.
How'd she become a squad captain, then?
She must have some incredible power that's invisible to the eye.
Rill Beaumontier. Captain of the Aqua Deer.
Isn't he kinda young?
A bit. Captain Rill is nineteen years old.
Nineteen? Really? Just four years older than I am!
Yeah! I'll be the Wizard King before I know it!
The Wizard King, huh? Now that's dreaming big.
But as for the person next in line...
If you take a look up there, you'll see. That's the Front Runner.
Captain of the Golden Dawn.
Said to be the mightiest Magic Knight Squad.
William Von Jens.
He has his squad members' complete trust.
I hear it was Captain William who took the enemy general's head in that battle a while back.
Man, it would be awesome to get into the Golden Dawn!
That or the Silver Eagles!
Don't be an idiot.
Rills and Elite Nobles are the only ones who ever get into those squads.
Let's get this over with. The sooner we start, the sooner we'll be done.
This exam is going to decide these youth's futures.
You really shouldn't be taking it so lightly.
You take it seriously enough for all of us.
All the Captains here in one place.
Each of the Magic Knight Squad Captains is said to be more powerful than a hundred mages combined.
From their illustrious ranks will come the next Wizard King.
And the Wizard King?
Like he would bother with something as pedestrian as an exam.
Just getting all the Squad Captains in one place is miraculous already.
Attention examinees!
Thank you for waiting.
I will be administering this year's entrance exam.
Magic Trees Descent!
Surprise! Surprise! Amazing as usual.
Right now, this man is the one closest to becoming the Wizard King.
You've waited long enough.
The time has come. Let the entrance exam begin!
In just a few moments, we'll begin the first in a series of tests.
The nine Magic Knight Captains will be serving as your judges.
And when the exam is complete, we will choose the individuals we want on our squads.
If chosen, you are in. If more than one squad chooses you, you will decide which you would like to join.
However, if you are not selected by any squad, that means you have been deemed unqualified to join the Magic Knights.
That won't happen. I will be chosen.
And now for your first test. You must use the brooms you've been given to fly.
To fly?
I've never done that before.
A mage who is in control of his or her magic power can do it on instinct alone.
It is our most basic way to get from one place to another.
If you can't fly on a broom, then you are not worth our time.
Enough talk. Now begin!
This test is an excellent way for us to gauge the examinee's basic abilities.
Seems we have a number of promising candidates this year.
Hard to believe a guy from some backwater village could do so well.
He was chosen by the four-leaf clover.
What's going on there? Even if he doesn't have any significant talent, he should still be able to float.
If you'll excuse me for a moment.
Can you believe this guy?
Well, that's one down at least.
Why did he even bother to come?
Hey, what are you doing? This is supposed to be the easy part.
Try relaxing your muscles a bit. See? It really couldn't be simpler.
Wow! Man, that's so awesome!
Don't tense up. Let it come naturally.
Right! Got it! You're a good guy, you know?
Nope! Still not happening!
Right.
What are you doing?
I just… I mean…
Don't play dumb with me. I've told you royalty need not undergo the same tests as common folk.
Yes, but…
Enough. Where you'll go is already decided. Stop this pointless nonsense.
Yes. Of course, Nozel.
Although, if we're being honest, your very existence is pointless.
It's fine! Try to relax!
Shake it off and keep going!
I'm not done yet!
Well, what's next?
Nope! Still not giving up!
On to the next test. The final and most difficult. A display of combat skill.
Prepare to duel!
You will break into pairs and fight each other! Use your grimoires to attack and defend!
I bet losing will tank your chances of being chosen. Better to choose an easy partner. Someone weak.
As knights, battle is our business. We want to see everything you're capable of!
The test will end when one combatant either surrenders or is unable to continue. We have mages wielding recovery magic standing by for the injured.
So don't hold anything back!
The last test? I've done nothing but shout this whole time! The best way to show off now is to pair off with someone strong! There's gotta be someone who'll agree to fight me!
Ha ha! What do you say you and I pair up?
You really mean it, Seke? You're willing to take on a charity case like me?
Oh, absolutely! Ha ha!
You really are a good guy!
We're ready for the first bout. Let's go!
We're coming!
Ha ha!
We're both working for the same goal! So we'll have a fair fight but nobody pulls any punches, okay?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Stop trying so hard. It's almost getting painful to watch. You're just a grubby little gutter rat who's way out of his depth.
I guess I should thank you for sticking around and making me look good. Once I'm chosen by a squad, I plan to kick up my heels and enjoy the ride.
It's going to be so much fun.
No. Let's get this over with, shall we?
Then you can scurry on home to the garbage heap you came from and get back to whatever pitiful excuse for a life you have left.
Ha ha!
Man, he had the right idea. Picking the weakest partner to duel.
Oh, Seke.
Now! Beacon!
No pulling punches, remember? Let's do this, Asta!
Ha ha!
Bronze Creation Magic! Seke Magnum Cannonball!
What do you think of this, Captains?
The bronze magic power I've crafted is dual purpose.
It protects me and attacks with magic bullets.
It will fend off his pathetic attacks, showing off my skills at defense.
Then, the second he's exhausted, I'll go on the offensive and shoot!
That seems like some fairly high level magic for an examinee.
He looks like an insect though. Big spiny pill bug.
Come on, don't get shy on me now. Ha ha!
Good. Watching him struggle should liven things up.
Okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
Ah!
Unlike you, Seke.
I'm not joining the magic knights just so I can slack off and have a little fun!
I've got a much bigger goal!
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
My sweetheart, I'm gonna be the Paper King!
come standing on board and tuck it in
every day!
You can bend 최鮮感 the size of the board
through somehow opening has something in the place.
狭い教室で 今日も主役が輝いた 僕は眩しくて目を閉じる
散々考えた 革命は手の中に おかしいだろう
笑いたければ 笑えばいいから
残された僕らは 何かになりたくて
いつまでも いつまでも 同じ朝を迎えてる
明日を選ぶのは 君自身しかいないよ
超えていこう 今日までの僕らを
オスタ vs. the Anti-Birds
up!